http://www.webmineralshop.com/it/content/2-note-legali

Cart
More products »
0
Carrello
0
Elemento(i)
35,00 €
Rubellite , Jonas Mine, Conselheiro Pena, Minas...
45,00 €
Webminerals S.A.S Policy & Privacy Statement
Our Customer can exercise the right of withdrawal pursuant to Art. 5 of Legislative Decree N° 185/99of Italian law
The Customer can withdraw from the purchase contract and return the goods purchased
within a time limit of 10 working days such days starts upon Customer’s receipt of the goods.
The right of withdrawal is exercised by sending written notice , within the time limit , to Webminerals S.A.S  by  e-mail.We will notify the Customer within 48 hours thereafter.
The specimen/s must be returned in perfect condition within 15 days from the date of the notice of withdrawal. It must also contain  all   material, including the original packaging. (Invoice, labels ...)
The return of goods is understood to be at the care and expense of the Customer who decides to withdraw from the contract.
Webminerals S.A.S shall have a 30 day time limit from the date of receipt of the returned products for crediting to the Customer the sum it had paid, less  shipping costs.
Protection of Privacy
Every time an order is issued, the person consents to the use of personal data only for commercial, fiscal, administrative, and informative purposes pertraining to our business activity, according to article 13 of Italian law 196 30/06/2003. (PROTECTION OF PERSONS AND OTHER SUBJECTS WITH RESPECT TO TREATMENT OF PERSONAL DATA)
According to this law  and with reference to personal data obtained or to be obtained in the future, we indicate the following:
The obtaining and use of personal data has the exclusive purpose of permitting us to  perform a correct business service consequently such data are and will be treated, either on computer or on paper, in a manner that is licit and correct, respecting the law.
The data can be communicated to third organizations (i.e. banks or organizations connected to us) exclusively for the development of our fiscal report.
The data can always be updated, modified,   by writing an email message to us
The title holder of your data is Webminerals S.A.S with administrative offices in via mameli 56 - 15066 GAVI - AL - ITALY   Tax id: 01961370069
COOKIES INFORMATION
This Notice is provided for the purposes set out in Article. 13 of the Italian Privacy Code ((Legislative Decree no. 196 of 30/06/2003)), taking into account the provision of the Guarantor "Simplified Arrangements to Provide Information and Obtain Consent Regarding Cookies - May, 8 - 2014 "
WHAT IS A COOKIE?
A cookie is a tiny file that stores information on your computer when you visit a web site. You can find out more about cookies by visiting http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. Cookies enable us to improve our service to you, estimate our audience size and usage patterns, store information about your preferences and recognize you when you return to our site.
By using our site, you agree to our use of cookies. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies (or just to refuse third party cookies), but if you do this you may not be able to enjoy full use of the site and you may not be able to take advantage of certain promotions we may run from time to time. Scroll down for information on how to manage cookies in standard browsers.
WHAT COOKIES ARE SET ON THIS WEBSITE?
The table below shows all of the cookies that might be set by us when you visit our site and why we use them.
Cookies
Description
Session Cookies
Are used by the server to store information about user page activities so users can easily pick up where they left off on the server's pages. By default, web pages really don't have any 'memory'. Cookies tell the server what pages to show the user so the user doesn't have to remember or start navigating the site all over again. Cookies act as a sort of â€œbookmarkâ€ within the site. Similarly, cookies can store ordering information needed to make shopping carts work instead of forcing the user to remember all the items the user put in the shopping cart.
TO DISABLE ALL COOKIES
You can refuse consent to the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser.The following section provides links that explain how to disable cookies for the most popular browsers (for other browsers, we suggest looking for the option in the help section of the software).
Internet Explorer :  http://windows.microsoft.com/en-IN/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11
Google Chrome :  https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en
Mozilla Firefox :    https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences
Opera :  http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/
Apple Safari :    :    https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US& locale=it_IT
YOU CAN MEET US
ROME  7 & 8 Dic
Specials
No Special products
Facebook
Newsletter
Sign up today for free and be the first to get notified on our new updates, discounts and special Offers.
Go!
Ok
Vi informiamo che il nostro negozio online utilizza i cookies e non salva nessun dato personale automaticamente, ad eccezione delle informazioni contenute nei cookies.
Webminerals
About us
Privacy
Our stores
Note Legali
Catalog
Specials
New products
Webminerals s.a.s di G. Signorelli &C.
There are no products selected for comparison.
Close
Compara
Search
More products »
More products »
